EditPlus Text Editor v3.20
==========================
Copyright © 1998-2010 ES-Computing
Homepage: http://www.editplus.com/
E-mail: support@editplus.com

What is EditPlus
----------------
EditPlus is a text editor, HTML editor and programmers editor for 
Windows. While it can serve as a good Notepad replacement, it also 
offers many powerful features for Web page authors and programmers.

* Syntax highlighting for HTML, CSS, PHP, ASP, Perl, C/C++, Java,
  JavaScript and VBScript. Also, it can be extended for other
  programming languages based on custom syntax files.

* Seamless Web browser for previewing HTML pages, and FTP commands for
  uploading local files to FTP server.

* Other features include HTML toolbar, user tools, line number, ruler,
  URL highlighting. auto-completion, cliptext, column selection,
  powerful search and replace, multiple undo/redo, spell checker,
  customizable keyboard shortcuts, and more.

SHAREWARE
---------
EditPlus is not free software. You may use this software for
evaluation purposes without charge for a period of 30 days. If you use
this software after the 30 day evaluation period, you must pay
registration fee. See 'How to register' on the Online Manual.

Distribution
------------
You may distribute the evaluation version of this software and
documentation in its unmodified form via electronic means. But you
should not charge or requesting donations for any such copies however
made and from distributing the software and/or documentation with
other products without the author's written permission.

System Requirement
------------------
* Windows XP/2003/Vista/7 or higher.

Spell Checker
-------------
You can download spell checker from our web site.
http://www.editplus.com/download.html

The Sentry Spelling-Checker Engine
Copyright © 1999 Wintertree Software Inc.

Remove
------
Run 'Uninstall' on the EditPlus Start Menu folder or open 'Add/Remove
Programs' in Control Panel and double-click 'EditPlus 3' in the list
box.

Feedback
--------
For feedback, questions and any comments:
- E-mail    support@editplus.com
- Homepage  http://www.editplus.com/


===== README IN SIMPLIFIED CHINESE =====


EditPlus 文本编辑器 v3.20
=========================
版权所有 © 1998-2010 ES-Computing
官方主页: http://www.editplus.com/
电子邮件: support@editplus.com

EditPlus 简介
-------------
EditPlus 是 Windows 下的一个文本编辑器、HTML 编辑器以及程序设计员的编辑
器。它不但是记事本的一个很好的代替工具，同时它也为网页作者和程序设计员提
供了许多强大的功能。

* 对 HTML、CSS、PHP、ASP、Perl、C/C++、Java、JavaScript 和 VBScript 的语
  法突出显示。同时，根据自定义语法文件它能够扩展支持其它程序语言。

* 无缝网络浏览器预览 HTML 页面，以及 FTP 命令上载本地文件到 FTP 服务器。

* 其它功能包括 HTML 工具栏、用户工具栏、行号、标尺、URL 突出显示、自动完
  成、素材文本、列选择、强大的搜索和替换、多重撤销/重做、拼写检查、自定
  义快捷键，以及更多其它功能。

共享软件
--------
EditPlus 不是自由软件。您可以在三十天内以评估用途方式免费使用此软件。
若您想在三十天评估周期过后继续使用此软件，您必需购买授权许可证。请在
联机指南上查看“如何注册”。

分发
----
您可以通过电子方式分发该软件的评估版本及其未修改过的文件。但您不能因为
这种复制而要求任何的收费或捐款，以及没有作者的书面许可而与其它产品一起
分发该软件和/或文件。

系统要求
--------
* Windows XP/2003/Vista/7 或更新版本。

拼写检查程序
------------
您可以从我们的网站下载拼写检查程序。
http://www.editplus.com/download.html

The Sentry Spelling-Checker Engine
版权所有 © 1999 Wintertree Software Inc.

删除
----
运行 EditPlus 开始菜单上的“Uninstall”或在控制面板中打开“添加或删除
程序”然后在列表框中双击“EditPlus 3”。

反馈
----
要反馈信息、问题和任何意见：
- 电子邮件  support@editplus.com
- 官方主页  http://www.editplus.com/


===== README IN HANGUL(KOREAN) =====


에디트플러스란

에디트플러스는 인터넷 환경에서 편리하게 사용할 수 있는 윈도우용 문서
편집기로서, 메모장을 대신할 뿐 아니라 웹문서나 프로그램 개발을 쉽게 할
수 있도록 도와주는 많은 기능들을 지원합니다.

* HTML, CSS, PHP, ASP, Perl, C/C++, 자바, 자바스크립트, VB스크립트
  파일에서 구문 강조 기능을 지원합니다. 사용자가 직접 작성한 구문
  파일을 추가하여 다른 프로그래밍 언어도 지원할 수 있습니다.

* HTML 문서의 내용을 확인해 볼 수 있는 내장 브라우저와, 작성한 문서를
  FTP 서버로 업로드할 수 있는 FTP 기능을 지원합니다.

* 이 밖에 HTML 도구모음, 사용자 도구, 줄 번호, 눈금자, URL 강조, 자동
  완성, 클립텍스트, 칸 단위 선택, 강력한 찾기와 바꾸기, 다중 실행
  취소및 재실행, 사용자 정의 단축키 등 다양한 기능들을 쉽고 편리하게
  사용할 수 있습니다.

쉐어웨어

에디트플러스는 쉐어웨어로 배포되므로 누구나 자유롭게 다운로드 받아서
30일 동안 사용해 볼 수 있습니다. 만일 프로그램이 유용하다고 판단되어
30일 평가 기간 이후에도 계속 사용하고자 할 경우에는 제작자에게
등록비를 지불하여 정식 사용자로 등록해야 합니다. 온라인 매뉴얼의 '등록
방법' 항목을 참고하십시오.

배포

이 소프트웨어의 평가판은 자유롭게 복사할 수 있고 누구에게나 수정되지
않은 원본을 무료로 복사해 줄 수 있으며 전자적인 수단을 통해 무료로
배포할 수 있습니다. 그러나 제작자의 서면 동의 없이 그러한 복사 및
배포에 대한 대가로 요금을 부과해서는 안됩니다.

시스템 요구 사항

* 윈도우 2000/XP/Vista 또는 상위 버전

영문 철자 검사기

다음 웹사이트에서 영문 철자 검사기를 다운로드 받을 수 있습니다.
http://www.editplus.com/kr/download.html

The Sentry Spelling-Checker Engine
Copyright © 1999 Wintertree Software Inc.

제거하기

시작 메뉴의 EditPlus 항목에서 'Uninstall' 를 실행시키거나, 제어판에서
'프로그램 추가/삭제' 를 연 후 목록 상자에서 'EditPlus 3' 를 더블클릭
합니다.

피드백

문의사항이 있으시면 다음 전자메일 주소로 보내 주십시오.
* E-mail    support@editplus.com
* Homepage  http://www.editplus.com/kr/
